Guide to the Rust Engineering Company Records, 1905-1989 AIS.2006.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- President's Office Files, 1940-1949; VI.
  To complete this work, Rust had to navigate the many restrictions and regulations on the use of raw materials, and a significant amount of correspondence is dedicated to dealing with rationing boards and securing salaries for workers. Private work did continue, and Rust built boiler houses, blast furnaces, and stove foundations for steel mills.
  Most wartime work was overseen by S.M. Rust, Jr., who was vice-president at the time. S.M. Rust, Sr. did not retire from the presidency until 1945, when he became Chairman of the Board of Directors.
  Rust Engineering's opportunities for jobs only rose after the war, as it repaired overworked machinery and converted now-obsolete war factories into peacetime enterprises. As the nation entered the Space Age, the company also worked on nuclear energy projects and structures for NASA.
  The files taper off and end by 1949. It is possible that records from the 1950s went on to Litton Industries, which purchased Rust in 1967. Some information about Rust's activities during the 1950s and beyond can be found in Series VIII.
  - Correspondence, 1.
    Records from the 1940s are made up almost entirely of Day Files, consisting of copies of outgoing correspondence written by S.M. Rust, Jr., and interoffice files containing both incoming and outgoing mail. There are no job files and few subject files, but despite the limitations a great deal of information about company activity can be found in the correspondence. The interoffice files are much more extensive than earlier, possibly because of better record keeping techniques, but more likely because the offices had to work together constantly to keep up with government projects; many letters were sent between branch offices every day, often by airmail, as Rust coordinated numerous jobs around the country.
    - General Correspondence, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - S.M. Rust, Jr. Day File, January-December 1940 (Box 46, Folder 02-04)
    - S.M. Rust and S.M. Rust, Jr. Day File, January-October 1940 (Box 46, Folder 05-06)
    - S.M. Rust and S.M. Rust, Jr. Correspondence, January-December 1940 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Daily reports from Pittsburgh Office to S.M. Rust, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - S.M. Rust, Jr., personal, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Interoffice correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Birmingham Office correspondence, January-December 1940 (Box 47, Folder 02-04)
    - Los Angeles Office correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - New York Office correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Washington, D.C. Office correspondence, October-December 1940 (Box 47, Folder 07-08)
    - Windsor Office correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - General correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - S.M. Rust and S.M. Rust, Jr. Day File, January-December 1941 (Box 48, Folder 02-04)
    - Daily reports from Pittsburgh Office to SMR, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Daily Reports from SMR, Jr. to SMR, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Birmingham Office correspondence, January-March 1941 (Box 48, Folder 07-09)
    - Birmingham Office correspondence, April-November 1941 (Box 49, Folder 01-08)
    - Birmingham Office correspondence, December 1941 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Office correspondence, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 02-03)
    - Los Angeles Office correspondence, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Montreal Office correspondence, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - New York Office correspondence, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 06-07)
    - Washington, D.C. Office correspondence, January-June 1941 (Box 50, Folder 08-09)
    - Washington, D.C. Office correspondence, July-December 1941 (Box 51, Folder 01-02)
    - General correspondence, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - W.B. Gillies correspondence, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 04-06)
    - S.M. Rust personal correspondence, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - S.M. Rust, Jr. and Day File, First-Second Quarter, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 08-09)
    - S.M. Rust, Jr. and Day File, Third Quarter, 1942 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Interoffice correspondence, January-December 1942 (Box 52, Folder 02-04)
    - Birmingham Office correspondence, January-March 1942 (Box 52, Folder 05-07)
    - Birmingham Office correspondence,April-September, 1942 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Birmingham Office correspondence, October-December 1942 (Box 54, Folder 01-03)
    - Los Angeles Office correspondence, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - New York Office correspondence, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Philadelphia Office correspondence, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Washington, D.C. Office correspondence, January-February 1942 (Box 54, Folder 07-08)
    - Washington, D.C. Office correspondence, March-April 1942 (Box 55, Folder 01-05)
    - Washington, D.C. Office correspondence, May-December 1942 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence, 1943 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - S.M. Rust, Jr. Day File, First-Third Quarter, 1943 (Box 55, Folder 07-09)
    - S.M. Rust, Jr. Day File, Fourth Quarter, 1943 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Interoffice, First Quarter, 1943 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Interoffice, Third-Fourth Quarter, 1943 (Box 56, Folder 03-04)
    - Birmingham Office correspondence, January 1943 (Box 56, Folder 05-09)
    - Birmingham Office correspondence, June-December 1943 (Box 57, Folder 01-07)
    - Los Angeles Office correspondence, 1943 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - New York Office correspondence, 1943 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Washington, D.C. Office correspondence, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 01-02)
    - General correspondence, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 03-04)
    - S.M. Rust, Jr. correspondence, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - S.M. Rust, Jr. Day File, Second-Fourth Quarter, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 06-08)
    - S.M. Rust, Jr. correspondence, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - General correspondence, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - S.M. Rust Day File, January-September 1945 (Box 58, Folder 11-13)
    - S.M. Rust Day File, October-December 1945 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - S.M. Rust General Correspondence, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - S.M. Rust Day File, First-Fourth Quarter, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 03-06)
    - S.M. Rust Interoffice, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Interoffice, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - S.M. Rust Day File, January-December 1947 (Box 59, Folder 09-10)
    - S.M. Rust, Jr. personal file, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - S.M. Rust Day File, January-December 1948 (Box 60, Folder 02-03)
    - Birmingham Office correspondence, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - S.M. Rust Day File, January-December 1949 (Box 60, Folder 05-06)
    - S.M. Rust Personal File, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - S.M. Rust, Jr. personal file, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - S.M. Rust personal correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Subject Files, 2.
    - Salary raises and financial information, 1940-1942 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Contracts, 1940-1942 (Box 60, Folder 11-12)
    - Board of Directors and Stockholders Meeting minutes, 1940 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Daily reports from H.J. Bawser to S.M. Rust, April-May 1940 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Job application by prisoner Walker Buckner, 1940 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Salary Records, 1940-1942 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Completed questionnaire on construction practices for Associated General Contractors of America, 1941 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Legal information handled by Bayard Baldridge, 1942 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Balance sheets, 1942 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Fuel oil rationing, 1942 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Gasoline rationing, 1943 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Insurance, 1943 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - War Department survey of personnel, services, completed projects, 1943 (Box 61, Folder 11-12)
    - Qualifications and histories of key personnel for Army records, 1943 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - China-America Council of Commerce and Industry, Inc., 1944 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Proposed international work in South America, 1944 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Law Office of Miller and Chevalier, 1944-1945 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Report to Reconstruction Finance Corporation Relative to Gadsden Ordnance Plant, Gadsden, Alabama, 1945 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Anthony Bruyaux -- post-war surplus plants, 1945 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Drawing: Oil and air piping layout for No. 7 periodic circular kiln, Harbison Walker Refectories, 1946 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Proposed incinerator for the Town of Leesburg, Virginia, 1946 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Wage and fuel expenses, 1947 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Birmingham Office analysis, 1939-1949 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Affiliate Companies, VII.
  This series contains documents related to Rust Engineering's many subsidiaries, franchises, and other affiliate companies. In the early 1920s, Rust Engineering was made up of several divisions and departments. As the company expanded, affiliates were formed to specialize in specific services. This enabled the company to effectively handle, for example, both the construction work and the electrical work on a single plant, or to manufacture the brick that the Chimney Department required rather than purchase it from another company. Most subsidiaries could also take jobs on their own and operate somewhat independently from the larger company.
  Rust Engineering's first subsidiary was the Rust Furnace Company, which was created from the Furnace Division in 1927. Known for its patented triple-fired continuous furnace, which could heat steel from above and below at a rapid rate, the Rust Furnace Company could also custom-design, engineer, install, and repair all other types of industrial furnaces. The company provided furnaces for many of Pittsburgh's steel mills as well as for companies as far away as New Zealand and South Africa. Other successful subsidiaries include the Allegheny Industrial Electrical Company, which installed electrical systems for large plants, and the Vibroflotation Foundation Company, which used a unique process to build foundations on unstable ground by injecting sand into soil.
  The series also contains information on Coppee-Rust, a joint subsidiary created in 1962 by the Rust Engineering Company and Evence Coppee et Compagnie, an engineering and construction firm based in Brussels, Belgium. Coppee-Rust was a design and construction company which specialized in assisting American businesses interested in expanding outside of the U.S. It built plants in Belgium, Iraq, Qatar, the USSR, and many other countries. The formation of Coppee-Rust represents Rust Engineering's first attempt to merge its services with those of another independent corporation.
  Materials in this series have been arranged alphabetically by subsidiary or affiliate name and may include correspondence, reports, minute books, and promotional items, as well as technical information about the processes in which each subsidiary specialized.
  - Allegheny Industrial Electrical Company
    - Contracts, 1946-1955 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Promotional leaflets, c1950s-1960s (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Catalog of expense report sheets, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Financial statements, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Birmingham Clay Products Company
    - Correspondence between S.M. Rust and Lee Rust, 1925-1938 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 1921-1938 (Box 62, Folder 12-15)
    - "Hard Times" correspondence, 1932-1935 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1936-1940 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Balance sheets, 1920-1929 (Box 63, Folder 03-04)
    - Cost sheets, 1921-1930 (Box 63, Folder 05-06)
    - U.S. Department of Justice -- brick for a chimney (#1859), Atlanta, Georgia, 1927 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Expenses, 1927 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Report: Building Brick Manufacture in the District of Birmingham, Alabama, by H. Doolittle and Stanley N. Brown, Jr., 1928 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Statements of income, profit, and loss, 1930 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Blueprint: North Birmingham Plant of Birmingham Clay Products Co., July 12, 1930 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - W. R. Culbertson, furnace inventor, 1931-1935 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Bond holder agreement, 1933 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Indemnity and bond agreements, 1936-1939 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Audit report, 1940 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Bankruptcy and reorganization, 1940-1941 (Box 63, Folder 16-17)
    - Bankruptcy and reorganization, 1940-1941 (Box 64, Folder 01-02)
    - Balance sheet and statement of income, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Report on examination of accounts, June 30, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Reports on Examination of Financial Statements and Additional Information, 1968-1976 (Box 64, Folder 05-06)
    - Correspondence and balance sheets, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Bolivar Clay Products Company
    - Correspondence, 1921-1931 (Box 64, Folder 08-09)
    - Incoming correspondence, 1930-1931 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Property and taxes, 1921-1924 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Bolivar Clay Products Company Cumulative Preferred Stock Certificates, 1921-1946 (Box 65, Oversize 1)
    - Bolivar Clay Products Company Common Stock Certificates, 1921-1958 (Box 65, Oversize 2)
    - Coal Lease, Newport Coal Company, 1921-1924 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Blueprints and plans for Bolivar Manufacturing Plant, 1922 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Financial information, 1922-1926 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Amendments to the Certificate of Incorporation, 1932-1949 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Company reorganization, 1959 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Agreements between Bolivar and Woodbridge Clay Companies, 1959-1962 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Brick and Tile Manufacturing Company
    - Correspondence, 1930-1931 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Proposed bylaws, 1931 (Box 66, Folder 08-09)
    - Incorporation and stockholder information, 1931 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Coppee-Rust
    - Correspondence, 1961-1968 (Box 67, Folder 01-07)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1974 (Box 68, Folder 01-02)
    - Promotion Commerciale A Hasselt (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Commercial Promotion in Lille (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Delta Phi Fraternity -- dormitory, Lehigh University, Bethlehem, PA, 1963-1966 (Box 68, Folder 05-06)
    - Rust Engineering Company, Ltd., Great Britain, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Brochures, Rust Engineering Company, Ltd., Croydon, Surrey, c1965 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - European Economic Community and Evence Coppee & Compagnie, March 15, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Objective: European Expansion: A Profile of the Engineering and Construction Services of Coppee-Rust (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Annual reports of Coppee-Rust and Coppee, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Annual reports of Coppee-Rust and Coppee-affiliated companies, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Social and financial reports, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Etude et Construction Evence Coppee-Rust S.A (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Coppee-Rust-Damiron Group promotional book, c1963 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Coppee-Rust promotional book, c1963 (Box 69, Volume 1)
  - Doyle and Russell, Incorporated
    - Financial statements, 1965, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Howard R. Wright & Associates
    - Financial statements, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Loudon Rust
    - Bids on school building jobs, financial reports, 1930-1931 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Mason-Rust
    - Promotional brochure, 1950s (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Penwick Distillery Company
    - Proposed company structure, 1933 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Potomac Clay Products Company
    - Incorporation and organization, 1930-1931 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 70, Folder 08-09)
    - Annual reports, 1931-1937 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Blueprint: Proposed Arrangement of Machinery, Woodbridge, VA, February 17, 1937 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Blueprint: Proposed Flow Sheets, April 1930 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Waterfront property, Georgetown: acquisition and management, 1929-1941 (Box 71, Folder 02-03)
    - Registration in Virginia, 1930-1938 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Federal taxes, 1935 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Meeting minutes, 1936 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - H.B. Rust estate settlement, 1937 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Dissolution, 1938 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Potomac Real Estate Company
    - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Process Engineering Division
    - Promotional brochures, c1950s (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Rust Associates, Ltd.
    - Financial statements, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Rust Building, Inc.
    - Financial statements, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Lease of property, 1960s (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Dissolution, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Rust Construction Company
    - Incorporation and organization, 1927-1938 (Box 72, Folder 02-03)
    - Meeting minutes, 1927 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - State registration, 1930-1933 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Meeting minutes and dissolution, 1934-1938 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Rust Engineering Company (Canada) Ltd.
    - Financial statements, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Report Covering the Present and Future Power Plant Expansion Program for Ford Motor Company of Canada, Ltd., 1937 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Rust Furnace Division, Rust Furnace Company
    - Patent Agreements, 1929 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Continuous Furnaces Promotional brochure, c1930s (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Division correspondence and reports on refractory purchases, 1930-1931 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Rust Engineering vs. Chapman-Stein Corporation, patent infringement on soaking pit design, c1930 (Box 73, Folder 04-05)
    - Patent infringement on furnace design, 1932-1935 (Box 73, Folder 06-07)
    - Blueprints: Details of Brick Shapes, Rust Zone Controlled Triple Fired Continuous Recuperative Slab Reheating Furnace for Ford Co., 1934 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Profits and losses, 1936 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1940-1943 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Wartime salary regulations, 1943-1945 (Box 73, Folder 11-13)
    - Promotional booklet, 1944 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Rust Furnace vs. Loftus Engineering, patent infringement on furnace design, 1947 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Rust Furnace Company: Pioneers in Furnace Design promotional brochure, c1955 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Financial statements, 1956-1966 (Box 74, Folder 02-04)
    - Brochures and photographs, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Rust-Escher Hollow Fin Metallic Recuperators promotional brochure, c1960s (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Rust Gunite Company
    - Correspondence and expense reports, 1930 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Rust International Corporation
    - Promotional brochure, c1980 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Rust Properties
    - Financial statements, 1964-1969 (Box 74, Folder 09-10)
    - Dissolution, 1969-1970 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Vibroflotation Foundation Company
    - Promotional brochures, c1955 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Financial statements, 1965-1966 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Woodbridge Clay Products Company
    - Production and average cost of manufacturing brick, 1939-1946 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Publicity, 1920-1989; VIII.
  Series VIII consists of published newspaper and journal articles, advertisements, and booklets that represent the public face of Rust Engineering. Aimed at a wide audience of clients and the general public, they explain the services the company was capable of providing and describe some of its major successes. This series has been divided into two subseries, one for articles, and another for promotional items distributed by Rust.
  - Articles and Newspaper Clippings, 1942-1954; 1.
    Articles about Rust Engineering's projects and officers often appeared in the news. In order to keep track of what was published and how many people it reached, the company hired professional clipping services to collect articles from newspapers and trade journals. These were added to scrapbooks alongside copies of press releases and advertisements, and each article's circulation was recorded.
    Most articles announce contracts or describe successfully completed projects, often stressing the company's speed and utilization of current technology. Since there are very few files from the 1950s, these articles are the best source of information about the Rust Engineering's activity during that time. Paper mills, furnaces, and large plants were still the most common assignments, but there is also mention of the company's involvement with nuclear technology, including the construction of a massive spherical structure to house an atomic submarine's reactor during tests. Loose clippings and articles have also been included in this subseries.
    - Clipping Book, December 15, 1941-February 1, 1942 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Clipping Book, March-April 1942 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Clipping Book, July-August 1942 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Clipping Book, September-October 1942 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Clipping Book, October-December 1944 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Clipping Book, January-December 1946 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Clipping Book, January-December 1948 (Box 76, Folder 01-04)
    - Clipping Book, January-September 1949 (Box 76, Folder 05-07)
    - Clipping Book, October-December 1949 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Clipping Book, January-December 1950 (Box 77, Folder 02-05)
    - Clipping Book, January-September 1952 (Box 77, Folder 06-08)
    - Clipping Book, November 1952-March 1953 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Clipping Book, January-June 1954 (Box 78, Folder 02-03)
    - Clippings, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1940s (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Articles sent to Newspapers and Trade Journals, 1942-1957 (Box 78, Folder 06-10)
    - Articles sent to Newspapers and Trade Journals, 1965-1966 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Paper Mill Articles, 1950-1958 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Fortune articles, August 1960 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Contract Announcements, 1942 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Promotional Items, 1920-1989; 2.
    Rust Engineering published brochures and booklets for distribution to potential clients. They explain the company's services and experience and are often illustrated with diagrams and photographs of successful projects. This subseries contains examples of items that promote the company as a whole, but similar brochures for specific subsidiaries, such as the Rust Furnace Company, can be found in Series VII.
    - General Construction, c1920s (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Chimneys for All Purposes, c1920s (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Chimney brochures, 1938-1958 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Promotional leaflets for radial brick, waterproofing, gunite application, and other services, c1935 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - The Rust Engineering Company and the Rust Furnace Company, 1944 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - The Rust Engineering Company and Subsidiary Companies, c1954 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - The Rust Engineering Company: Engineers and Constructors for the Pulp and Paper Industry, 1954 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Promotional booklet for Birmingham Office, 1954 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - The Rust Engineering Company and Subsidiary Companies, c1956 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Experience Record of the Rust Engineering Company, c1960 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Promotional booklet for Birmingham Office, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Series of booklets on engineering, design, power plants, and steel mills, c1963 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Promotional booklet, c1975 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Promotional packet on construction, model building, and aerospace work, c1989 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Rust Promotional Calendars, 1944-1956 (Box 43.2, Oversize 02-12)
    - Industrial and Public Utility Engineering Projects Recently Executed by the Rust Engineering Company, Inc., 1930 (Oversize 13)
    - Industrial and Public Utility Engineering Projects Recently Executed by the Rust Engineering Company, Inc., 1938 (Oversize 14)
- Photographs, 1914-1967; IX.